<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Zoo Directory</string>
    <string name="lion_description">Lions have strong, compact bodies and powerful forelegs, teeth and jaws for pulling down and killing prey. Their coats are yellow-gold, and adult males have shaggy manes that range in color from blond to reddish-brown to black. The length and color of a lion\'s mane is likely determined by age, genetics and hormones.</string>
    <string name="default_animal_name">Lion</string>
    <string name="giraffe_description">Giraffes are the world\'s tallest mammals, thanks to their towering legs and long necks. A giraffe\'s legs alone are taller than many humans—about 6 feet . These long legs allow giraffes to run as fast as 35 miles an hour over short distances and cruise comfortably at 10 miles an hour over longer distances.</string>
    <string name="giant_panda_description">Giant pandas have a distinctive black and white coat, with black fur around their eyes and on their ears, muzzle, legs and shoulders. Their thick, wooly coat helps to keep them warm in their cool mountain homes. Adult pandas are about 150cm from nose to rump, with a 10-15cm tail.</string>
    <string name="monkey_description">Monkeys live in trees, grasslands, mountains, forests, and on high plains. A group of monkeys is called a troop. Most primates share six basic features: forward-facing eyes, eye sockets, grasping hands, nails, fingerprints, and large brains. Monkeys are most easily distinguished from apes by their tails.</string>
    <string name="elephant_description">Elephant, (family Elephantidae), largest living land animal, characterized by its long trunk (elongated upper lip and nose), columnar legs, and huge head with temporal glands and wide, flat ears. Elephants are grayish to brown in colour, and their body hair is sparse and coarse.</string>
    <string name="polar_bear_description">Polar bears are stocky, with a long neck, relatively small head, short, rounded ears, and a short tail. The male, which is much larger than the female, weighs 410 to 720 kg (900 to 1,600 pounds). It grows to about 1.6 metres (5.3 feet) tall at the shoulder and 2.2–2.5 metres in length.</string>
    <string name="penguin_description">Penguins are flightless seabirds that live almost exclusively below the equator. Some island-dwellers can be found in warmer climates, but most—including emperor, adélie, chinstrap, and gentoo penguins—reside in and around icy Antarctica. A thick layer of blubber and tightly-packed, oily feathers are ideal for colder temperatures.</string>
    <string name="crocodile_description">Crocodile, (order Crocodylia, or Crocodilia), any of 23 species of generally large, ponderous, amphibious animals of lizard-like appearance and carnivorous habit belonging to the reptile order Crocodylia. Crocodiles have powerful jaws with many conical teeth and short legs with clawed webbed toes. They share a unique body form that allows the eyes, ears, and nostrils to be above the water surface while most of the animal is hidden below. The tail is long and massive, and the skin is thick and plated.</string>
    <string name="zoo_name">Cheapest Zoo You\'ll Ever Find</string>
    <string name="zoo_phone_number_text">Call Us at (888) 888-888</string>
    <string name="zoo_phone_number">888-888-8888</string>
</resources>